HAFIZ MUHAMMAD AHMAD

LECTURER/MATHEMATICIAN



+92-3046629964



m.ahmad6593@gmail.com



Kot Molvi Abdul Qadir, Kasur

About Me

I am a dedicated and passionate Mathematics educator with a deeprooted commitment to fostering a love for mathematics in my students. With 3 years of experience in higher education, I have had the privilege of guiding and inspiring students to explore the beauty and practicality of mathematics.

Experience

Oxbridge College, Kasur 2020-2021

lecturer

I had the privilege of serving as a Mathematics Lecturer at Oxbridge College for one year. During my time there, I taught an intermediate mathematics course.

IQRA School, Kasur 2019 - 2020

Math Teacher/Coordinator

During my tenure as a Mathematics Teacher at IQRA School, I had the opportunity to instruct and inspire students in the subject of mathematics for one year.

Education

2019 - 2021 MSc Mathematics

University of Education, Township Campus, Lahore

2017 - 2019 BSc Mathematics & Physics

Punjab University, Lahore

Language

English

Urdu

Punjabi

Expertise

- MS Office
- SEO
- leadership

Reference

Hafiz Ahmad Mujtaba

IQRA School/Principal

Phone

+92-3083387061